english-at-home.com 2019-03-16

# Privacy Policy | english-at-home.com

It is www.english-at-home.com's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we collect or which you provide to us. This privacy policy explains what types of personal information we receive, collect or use when you use and visit this site and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**The GDPR**

The EU General Data Protection Regulations (May 25 2018) give you much greater protection over your privacy and personal information. Here's what you need to know:

www.english-at-home.com are the "data controller". If you have any questions about this policy or about how we use your Personal Data, please contact us via our contact details at the end of this policy.

Personal Data we collect via www.english-at-home.com  
We only collect Personal Data where you choose to sign up to receive free content, including tips to learn English, plus special offers on promotions. We do not share your email address with anyone else, and you can unsubscribe any time via the link in the email.

Data we collect automatically  
When you sign up to receive emails from us, we automatically record your IP address and time-stamp as proof of your consent.

We automatically collect certain information when you visit our website, such as the type of browser and operating system you are using, and the domain name of your ISP (internet service provider), the time you visited our site, and which pages you visited. We do not link this information with any personal data.

We may also collect data automatically through our use of cookies on the website. Google, as a third party vendor, uses advertising cookies to serve ads based on your previous visits to our website or other websites. You can opt out of personalised advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated)

Use of your Personal Data  
We will only use your Personal Data when the law allows us to.

Sharing your Personal Data  
We take your privacy seriously and will not share your Personal Data with others, except as  
permitted by applicable law or as set out below:  
We share Personal Data as necessary with third parties located outside the EU who provide services to us and who require the information to provide those services. These third parties may include social media advertising platforms or email service providers. Please note that we have appropriate data privacy safeguards in place with these third parties.

Keeping your Personal Data secure  
We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with applicable law, including the GDPR, to safeguard Personal Data from accidental loss, destruction or damage and unauthorised access, use and disclosure.

Retention periods for use of your Personal Data  
We will use and store your Personal Data only for as long as necessary. We review the Personal Data we hold at regular intervals and delete permanently or anonymise any Personal Data which is no longer necessary.

Children  
This website and our services are aimed at adults, and we do not knowingly collect any  
Personal Data relating to children aged under 15 years old. If you are under the age of 15,  
please do not provide us with any of your Personal Data, including your email address.

Access to and control over your Personal Data  
You have legal rights under applicable law in relation to your Personal Data. You can ask the  
following questions, or take the following actions, at any time by contacting us via email ( support @ english-at-home.com)  or via our postal address:  
• see what Personal Data we hold about you (if any), including why we are holding it and who  
it could be disclosed to;  
• ask us to change/correct your Personal Data;  
• ask us to delete your Personal Data;  
• object to the processing of your Personal Data;  
• ask us to restrict the processing of your Personal Data;  
• withdraw any consents you have given us to the processing of your Personal Data; and  
• express any concerns you have about third parties’ use of your Personal Data.

Change of purpose  
We will only use your Personal Data for the purposes for which we collected it, unless we  
reasonably consider that we need to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible  
with the original purpose. If you wish to have an explanation as to how the processing for  
the new purpose is compatible with the original purpose, please contact us.  
If we need to use your Personal Data for an unrelated purpose, we will notify you and we will  
explain the legal basis which allows us to do so.

Contact Us  
Our full details are:  
english-at-home.com LTD

Email for Privacy Questions:  
support @ english-at-home.com

Postal Address:  
5, The Chambers  
Vineyard  
Abingdon-on-Thames  
OXON OX14 3PX
